

DONTSIOS NIKOS

Software Developer

About Me

Hello, I'm Dontsios Nikos, a junior developer. Proficient in Python, HTML, CSS and Selenium. Committed to writing clean, efficient code, I bring a proactive problem-solving mindset and a passion for continuous learning to any team.

- 6942695659
- dontsiosnikolaos@gmail.com
- Marasli 16 A, Thessaloniki
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikosdontsios-606b2927a/
- https://github.com/Lockdphoenix

Language

- Greek
- English C2

Expertise

- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- MODX
- Selenium
- SeleniumBace
- GitHub
- Git

Experience

Family Business-Carpentry 2014-2023

Employment as an assistant in the family business of furniture manufacturing, installation and repair. Objects include loading/unloading materials, assembling, fitting, repairing, assembling and operating appropriate equipment.

AstroLabs Internship

2024-Now

Internship as a full stack developer, specialized at MODX, Wordpress and Prestashop.

Voluntary activity

Patriarchal Foundation for Patristic Studies 01/10/2018-30/06/2019

Responsible for guarding the museum area, reception and service of visitors and surveillance of security cameras of the exhibition area and the Monastery

Education

Cisco Networking Academy

Webinar in Python Programming Essentials 2022 - 2023

University Ecclesiastical Academy of Thessaloniki

Management of Ecclesiastical Relics and Christian Cultural Heritage 2014 - 2019

Skills Summary

Learning Programming Languages

Web Development

Database Management

Problem-solving and Debugging

Involvement with gaming-game design